Guide to the Susie Bright papers and On Our Backs records, 1978-2013.
Bright, Susie papers and On Our Backs records
- Videos
  - Afro Erotica vol. 10, 1987; V-6273 (Box 1)
    Annotation by Susie: "Christian Mann headed up a successful series called Afro Erotics to appeal to a black market and black actors. Distinguished because promoted black directors and the characters were presented as contemporary LA San Fernando Valley characters, rather than Southern antebellum caricatures. There are still racial cliches but it is a Genx generation point of view. "
  - Afro Erotica vol. 5, 1986; V-6274 (Box 1)
  - After Hours, 1995; V-6275 (Box 1)
  - All About Annette, 1982; V-6276 (Box 1)
    Annotation by Susie: "Anette Haven, regarded as one of the most beautiful actors of rated X. was an experienced speaker and has a fan club still today. Was politically active as a liberal feminist and animal rights supporter. Starred in many of the more serious dramas and tragedies in XXX golden years. Susie reviewed many of her careers in Forum. "
  - All about Gloria Leonard, 1978; V-6277 (Box 1)
    Annotation by Susie: "Gloria Leonard is one of the middle aged stars of the Golden Era of erotic films and she was a adult industry lobbyist on free of speech activist for decades. Very politically active as a feminist, free speech activist. She was one of the founders of Club 90, the first feminist porn star support group, formed in 1983. She currently lives on big island of Hawaii. Her first feature film with Radley Metzger, the "Opening of Misty Beethoven" was noted as one of the best of all time. "
  - All Girl Action, 1998; V-6278 (Box 1)
    Annotation by Susie: "Show and tell lecture on the history of lesbian eroticism in cinema featuring ~ 25 clips from 1967 Terese and Isabelle) - 1998 and contemporary lesbian made videos. Was first presented at the gay film festival of San Francisco to sold out crowd in 1998, featuring the original format for each clip 45 mm, 60mm, 65mm, Beta or VHS. Subsequently toured through American University, repertory theaters, British Film Institute, Hamburg and Bern gay film festival, banned in Australia. Susie was inspired by Vito Russo, who did the lecture slide show called the Celluloid Closet before he wrote his book. Future plans: Susie will present this show live at cornell in 2014 and will do a recording of the presentation. Education availability only"
  - All Girl Action, V-6581 (Box 11)
  - The Analyst, 1975; V-6279 (Box 1)
  - Angel in Mr. Holmes, 1988; V-6280 (Box 1)
    Annotation by Susie: Posthumous biopic on John Holmes illustrious career. One of the most well known actor in porn, despite rep for penis size, Holmes was probably famous at cunnilingus. More for getting women off than Holmes dick size. Interviews with some of costars and directors. The intent was to make a commercial X rated movie, capitalizing on his name, but it's actually a tender romantic portrait.
  - Anime', 1998; V-6281 (Box 1)
  - Anna Obsessed, 1977; DVD-864 (Box 1)
    Annotation by Susie: Anna Obsessed depicts a heroine in genuine crisis and forced sex. High production values and the combination of tragedy and sex made it a controversial film. Susie included in the first Good Vibrations video catalogue and defended its inclusion despite many customer complaints that it didn’t have a happy or redemptive ending. It remains an example of a XXX feature with high level drama aspirations.
  - Annie Sprinkle Ultimate…, ?; V-6283 (Box 1)
  - Annie Sprinkle's Herstory of Porn, 1999; V-6284 (Box 1)
  - Autobiography of a Flea, 1976; V-6285 (Box 1)
  - Avatars de Venus, 1993; DVD-865 (Box 1)
  - Bad Girl, V-6287 (Box 1)
  - Ballot Measure 9, 1995; V-6288 (Box 11)
  - Barbara Broadcast, 1977; V-6289 (Box 1)
  - Barbara Broadcast, 1977; V-6290 (Box 1)
  - Barbara Broadcast, 1977; V-6291 (Box 1)
  - Bathroom Sluts, 1998; V-6292 (Box 1)
  - Be Careful What You Wish For, 1994; V-6293 (Box 1)
  - Behind the Green Door The Sequel, 1986; V-6294 (Box 1)
  - Bend Over Boyfriend, 1998; V-6295 (Box 1)
  - Bend Over Boyfriend, 1998; V-6296 (Box 1)
  - Bend Over Boyfriend 2, 1999; V-6297 (Box 1)
  - Betty Dodson: Her Life of Sex and Art, 2007; DVD-866 (Box 1)
  - Betty Page: Setting the Record Straight, 1991; V-6299 (Box 1)
  - Bi and Beyond, 1988; V-6300 (Box 1)
  - Big Girls, 2000; V-6301 (Box 1)
  - Big Guns, 1987; V-6302 (Box 1)
  - Bilitis, 1977; V-6303 (Box 1)
    Annotation by Susie: this may be a PAL copy
  - Bittersweet, 1993; V-6304 (Box 1)
  - Bizarre, 1992; V-6305 (Box 1)
  - Black and White in Living Color, 1992; V-6306 (Box 1)
    Annotation by Susie: Graver was Orson Welles cinematographer.
  - Black Throat, 1985; V-6307 (Box 2)
  - Blonde Justice, 1993; V-6308 (Box 2)
  - The Blue Angel - German Version, 1930; V-6309 (Box 2)
  - The Blue Angel, 1959; V-6310 (Box 2)
  - Blue Angel, 1992; V-6311 (Box 2)
  - Blue Angel Part 2, 1992; V-6312 (Box 2)
  - Bobby Sox, 1996; V-6313 (Box 2)
  - Body Music, 1989; V-6314 (Box 2)
  - Bonnie and Clyde, 1993; V-6315 (Box 2)
  - Bound, the unrated version, 1996; V-6316 (Box 2)
  - Bound, 1996; V-6317 (Box 2)
  - Boys/Life, 1994; V-6318 (Box 2)
  - Bright, 1987; V-6319 (Box 2)
  - Burlezk unedited, ?; V-6320 (Box 2)
  - Café Flesh, 1982; V-6321 (Box 2)
  - Café Flesh #2, 1997; V-6322 (Box 2)
  - Candy Stripers, 1978; V-6323 (Box 2)
    Annotation by Susie: this may be early edition, in which case, its OOP
  - Candy Stripers, 1978; V-6324 (Box 2)
  - Candy Stripers, 1978; DVD-867 (Box 2)
  - Cat & Mouse, 1992; V-6326 (Box 2)
  - CBC Talk TV, ?; V-6327 (Box 11)
  - Celebrating Orgasm, 1996; V-6328 (Box 2)
  - Cherry, 1970; V-6329 (Box 2)
  - Celluloid Closet, 1995; V-6330 (Box 2)
  - Chloe Raw and Jack Tidbits, V-6578 (Box 11)
  - Cirque Noir, 2005; DVD-868,9 (Box 2)
  - Classic Films of Irving Klaw v. 1, 1984; V-6332 (Box 2)
  - Classic Films of Irving Klaw v. 2, 1984; V-6333 (Box 2)
  - Classics Erotica from the Past, V-6334 (Box 2)
  - Classics Erotica from the Past, V-6335 (Box 2)
  - Clips, ?; V-6336 (Box 2)
  - Clips, ?; V-6337 (Box 2)
  - Coming of Angels, 1977; V-6338 (Box 2)
  - Community Television of Santa Cruz County, V-6560 (Box 11)
  - Corrupt Beyond Innocence, 1990; V-6339 (Box 2)
  - Cult 70s Porno Director Zebedy Colt, 1995; DVD-870 (Box 2)
  - Current Flow, ?; V-6341 (Box 2)
  - Cutting Edge, 1993; V-6342 (Box 2)
  - Dangerous Women, V-6343 (Box 2)
  - Decadence, the Caballero title, 2006; V-6344 (Box 3)
  - Deep Inside Annie Sprinkle, 1981; V-6345 (Box 3)
  - Deep Inside Ashlyn Gere, 2002; V-6346 (Box 3)
  - Deep Inside Dirty Movies/Pictures, 1990; V-6347 (Box 11)
  - Deep Inside Vanessa Del Rio, 1986; V-6348 (Box 3)
  - Deep Inside Vanessa Del Riio, 1986; V-6349 (Box 3)
  - Deep Inside Chloe, 2002; V-6350 (Box 3)
  - Deep Inside Nikki Sinn, 1997; V-6351 (Box 3)
  - Deep Throat, 1990; V-6352 (Box 3)
  - Deep Throat II, 1974; V-6353 (Box 3)
  - Deep Throat, 1972; DVD-871 (Box 3)
  - Devil in Miss Jones, 1973; V-6355 (Box 3)
  - Devil in Miss Jones, 1973; V-6356 (Box 3)
  - Devil in Miss Jones, 1973; DVD-872 (Box 3)
  - Debbie Does 'Em All, 1984; V-6358 (Box 3)
  - Dildo Diaries, 2002; V-6359 (Box 3)
  - Dirty Movie, V-6360 (Box 10)
  - Dirty Minds, 1996; V-6361 (Box 3)
  - Disobedient Nancy, 1989; V-6362 (Box 3)
  - Dixie Ray, 1983; V-6363 (Box 3)
  - The Dr. Susan Block Show, 1993; V-6532 (Box 11)
  - Dream Walk, 1989; V-6364 (Box 3)
  - Ecstasy Girls, 1979; V-6365 (Box 3)
  - Erotic in Nature, 1985; V-6366 (Box 3)
  - Erotic In Nature, 1985; V-6367 (Box 3)
  - Eroticism in Cinema, 1987; V-6368 (Box 11)
    Annotation by Susie: This may be a video of SB in live lecture, in which case, (c) SB
  - Erotique, 1994; V-6369 (Box 3)
  - Erotique, 1994; V-6370 (Box 3)
  - Erotique, 1994; V-6371 (Box 3)
  - Erotique trailer, 1994; V-6372 (Box 3)
  - Eruption, 1984; V-6373 (Box 3)
  - Escape to Pleasure Island, 1998; V-6374 (Box 3)
  - Every Woman Has a Fantasy part 2, 1985; V-6375 (Box 3)
  - Every Woman Has a Fantasy, 1984; V-6376 (Box 3)
  - Exposed, 1990; V-6377 (Box 3)
  - Expressions of Love, 1981; V-6378 (Box 3)
  - Expert Guide to Rough Sex, 2008; DVD-873 (Box 3)
  - Eyes of Desire, 1998; V-6380 (Box 3)
    Annotation by Susie: Femme Productions
  - Female Athletes, 1980; V-6381 (Box 3)
  - Femme - Royalle Interview, V-6382 (Box 11)
  - Fire on the Mountain, 1992; V-6383 (Box 3)
  - Firecracker Alternative Book Awards 1996, 1996; V-6384 (Box 11)
    Annotation by Susie: Home movie of Susie receiving award for Nothing But the Girl at ABA, Art Photography Book of the Year
  - Firestorm, 1984; V-6385 (Box 3)
  - Fire Storm, 1984; V-6386 (Box 4)
  - Fiona on Fire, 1978; V-6387 (Box 4)
  - Frank Vickers vol. 1, 1986; V-6388 (Box 4)
    Annotation by Susie: dir. by Christopher Rage for his company Live Video
  - Frankenpenis, 1996; V-6389 (Box 4)
  - Freedom is Bondage, V-6390 (Box 11)
  - Fun With a Sausage, 1984; V-6391 (Box 4)
  - Gail Rich Awards 2002, 2002; V-6579 (Box 11)
  - Gemini Destiny, V-6392 (Box 4)
  - The Gift, 1997; V-6393 (Box 4)
  - The Gift, 1997; V-6394 (Box 4)
  - Girls of Porn, 1989; V-6395 (Box 4)
  - Girlworld, 2002; V-6396 (Box 4)
  - Good Vibrations II, 1991; V-6397 (Box 4)
  - Grafenberg Spot, 1985; V-6398 (Box 4)
  - Grapefruit Kathy, 1988; DVD-874 (Box 4)
  - Haight Ashbury 1967, 1967; V-6400 (Box 4)
  - Hard Love and How to Fuck in High Heals, 2000; V-6401 (Box 4)
  - Hay Fever, 1988; V-6402 (Box 4)
  - Healing Sex, 1999; DVD-882 (Box 11)
  - Heart Like a Wheel, 1983; V-6404 (Box 4)
  - Heavenly Hyapatia, 1990; V-6405 (Box 4)
  - Her Name was Lisa, 1980; V-6406 (Box 4)
  - History of the Blue Movie, 1970; V-6407 (Box 4)
  - History of the Blue Movie, 1970; V-6408 (Box 4)
  - Honey Pie, 1976; V-6409 (Box 4)
  - Hot Scalding, 1990; V-6410 (Box 4)
  - Hot Shots, 1998; V-6411 (Box 4)
  - House of Dreams, 1990; V-6412 (Box 4)
  - House of Dreams, 1995; V-6413 (Box 4)
  - How to Enlarge Your Penis, Original Ed., 1985; V-6414 (Box 4)
  - How to Enlarge Your Penis, 1992; V-6415 (Box 4)
  - How to Female Ejaculate, 1992; V-6416 (Box 4)
  - How to Female Ejaculate, 1992; V-6417 (Box 4)
  - HTFEC Off-line, V-6526 (Box 11)
  - How to Read a Dirty Movie, V-6580 (Box 11)
  - How to Read a Dirty Movie, V-6418 (Box 11)
  - How to Read a Dirty Movie, DVD-1061 (Box 11)
  - I A Woman, 1965; V-6419 (Box 4)
  - I Know What Girls Like, original ed., 1986; V-6420 (Box 4)
  - I Spit on Your Grave, 1978; V-6421 (Box 4)
  - I Spit on Your Grave, 1978; V-6422 (Box 5)
  - I, Rick, 1986; V-6423 (Box 5)
    Annotation by Susie: One-Handed Histories: The Eroto-Politics of Gay Male Video Pornography By John R. Burger
  - I:Rick, 1986; V-6424 (Box 5)
  - Icewoman, 1993; V-6425 (Box 5)
  - Insatiable, 1980; DVD-875 (Box 10)
  - Insatiable Janine, 1982; V-6427 (Box 5)
  - Inside Marilyn Chambers, 1975; V-6428 (Box 5)
  - Intimate Interviews, 1996; V-6429 (Box 5)
  - Japanese Highway Honeys, V-6430 (Box 5)
  - Japanese Kimono Girls, V-6431 (Box 5)
  - JF, V-6432 (Box 5)
  - Jim and Vern, 1976; V-6433 (Box 11)
    Annotation by Susie: Educational film, 1976, from National Sex Forum
  - John Wayne Bobbitt: uncut, 1994; V-6434 (Box 5)
  - John Holmes and the All Star Sex Queens, 1980; V-6435 (Box 5)
  - Joy, 1975; V-6436 (Box 5)
    Annotation by Susie: http://www.onesheetindex.com/movie_posters/sexploitation/joy_5670.html
  - Kim #1, Neighbor Girls, V-6437 (Box 5)
  - Kim, Neighbor Girls, V-6438 (Box 5)
  - Kim #3, Neighbor Girls, V-6439 (Box 5)
  - Kisses from Romania, 1996; V-6440 (Box 5)
  - Laputa/Ranma/Silent Mobus, 1995; V-6441 (Box 5)
  - Legends of Porn, 1987; V-6442 (Box 5)
  - Lesbian Erotica vol. 1, V-6443 (Box 5)
  - Lesbian Fat Fuckers, 1989; V-6444 (Box 5)
  - Lesbian Impress, 1990; V-6445 (Box 5)
    Annotation by Susie: Fatale Video
  - Let Me Tell Ya Bout Fat Chicks II, 1987; V-6446 (Box 5)
  - Lialeh, 1974; V-6447 (Box 5)
    Annotation by Susie: Aretha Franklin drummer and Motown staple, was black power deep throat
  - Liquid Sky, 1982; V-6448 (Box 10)
  - Live Nude Girls Unite, 2000; V-6449 (Box 5)
  - Linda Les and Annie, 1992; V-6450 (Box 5)
  - Lolita, V-6451 (Box 10)
  - Lonestar Eagles Folsom Street Fair, V-6452 (Box 5)
  - Lovers Massage, 1993; V-6453 (Box 5)
  - Love Scenes for Loving Couples, 1987; V-6454 (Box 5)
  - Machine Gun Bimbos, V-6455 (Box 10)
  - Matinee Idol, 1984; V-6456 (Box 6)
  - Madams New Maid, 2001; V-6457 (Box 5)
  - Mad Love, 1988; V-6458 (Box 6)
  - Man With a Maid, 1990; V-6459 (Box 6)
  - Man With a Maid, 1990; V-6460 (Box 6)
  - Masseuse, 1990; V-6461 (Box 6)
    Annotation by Susie: almost not released
  - Masseuse 2, 1994; V-6462 (Box 6)
  - Master Hyde, 1987; V-6463 (Box 6)
  - Memories Within Miss Aggie, 1974; V-6464 (Box 6)
  - Midnight Heat, 1982; V-6465 (Box 6)
  - Midnight Heat, 1982; V-6466 (Box 6)
  - Midnight Heat, 1982; V-6467 (Box 6)
  - Midnight Heat, 1982; V-6468 (Box 6)
    Annotation by Susie: Watkins, deceased, was a famous horror director
  - Moo Goo Gai Poon, 1993; V-6469 (Box 6)
  - More Reel People, 1984; V-6470 (Box 6)
  - More than a Mouthful: "Bound" show, V-6471 (Box 11)
  - My Masters, 1986; V-6472 (Box 6)
  - Naked Came the Stranger, 1975; V-6473 (Box 6)
  - Naked Came the Stranger, 1975; V-6474 (Box 6)
  - Naked Came the Stranger, 1975; V-6475 (Box 6)
  - Nasty Girls #9, 1995; V-6476 (Box 6)
  - Neon Nights, 1981; DVD-876 (Box 6)
  - Nice Girls Don't Do It, 1990; V-6478 (Box 6)
  - Night Dreams, 1981; V-6479 (Box 6)
  - Night of Hunger, 1983; V-6480 (Box 6)
  - Night of Seduction, 1995; V-6481 (Box 6)
  - Nightshift Nurses, 1989; V-6482 (Box 6)
  - Nightshift Nurses, 1989; V-6483 (Box 6)
  - Nutjob Nurses, 2002; V-6484 (Box 6)
  - The O Boys: Parties, Porn & Politics, 1999; V-6527 (Box 11)
  - Old Reliable, V-6485 (Box 6)
  - Old Reliable, V-6486 (Box 6)
  - Old Reliable, V-6487 (Box 6)
  - Only the Very Best on Film, 1993; V-6488 (Box 6)
    Annotation by Susie: produced to accompany Holliday’s reference book
  - Opening of Misty Beethoven, 1976; V-6489 (Box 6)
  - Opening of Misty Beethoven, 1976; V-6490 (Box 6)
  - Our Dinner with Andrea, 1987; V-6491 (Box 7)
  - Our Friend the Volt, 2001; V-6492 (Box 7)
  - Outlaw Ladies, 1981; V-6493 (Box 7)
  - Pammy and Tommy, V-6494 (Box 7)
  - Passions of Carol, 1975; V-6495 (Box 7)
  - Passion Within, 1987; V-6496 (Box 7)
  - Passon Within, 1987; V-6497 (Box 7)
  - Pauli Schell, 1975; V-6498 (Box 7)
  - Pauli Schell, 1975; V-6499 (Box 7)
  - Peril or Pleasure?, 1989; V-6500 (Box 11)
  - Perils/Mayhem, 1986/1987; V-6501 (Box 7)
    Annotation by Susie: http://movies.nytimes.com/movie/227987/Perils-Mayhem-and-Mercy-Three-Films-by-Abigail-Child/overview
  - Period Pieces, 1997; V-6502 (Box 7)
  - Personal Best, 1982; V-6503 (Box 7)
  - Platinum Paradise, 1981; V-6504 (Box 7)
  - Pleasure Beach, 1983; V-6505 (Box 7)
  - Posse, 1993; V-6506 (Box 7)
  - Porn 101, V-6507 (Box 11)
  - Portrait of Jeff Stryker, 1986; V-6508 (Box 7)
  - Previews Volume Two, 1982; V-6509 (Box 7)
  - Private Afternoons of Pamela Mann, 1974; V-6510 (Box 7)
  - Private Afternoons of Pamela Mann, 1974; V-6511 (Box 7)
  - Professional Janine, 1976; V-6512 (Box 7)
  - Private Pleasures/Shadows, 1986; V-6513 (Box 7)
  - Private Pleasures/Shadows, 1986; V-6514 (Box 7)
  - Punishment of Anne, 1975; V-6515 (Box 7)
    Annotation by Susie: also sold under different title, The Image, 1976
  - Q Balls, 1996; V-6516 (Box 7)
  - Queer: The Movie, 1990; V-6517 (Box 7)
  - The Quest, V-6518 (Box 7)
  - Raw Talent III, 1987; V-6519 (Box 7)
  - Redefining Beauty: a Documentary on Body Image, V-6520 (Box 11)
  - Resurrection of Eve, 1973; V-6521 (Box 7)
  - Rites of Passion, 1987; V-6522 (Box 7)
  - Roomates, 1982; V-6523 (Box 7)
  - Samurai Voyeur, 1998; V-6524 (Box 7)
  - Safe is Desire, 1993; V-6525 (Box 7)
  - Satisfiers of Alpha Blue, 1980; DVD-877 (Box 7)
  - Saturday Night at the Baths, 1975; DVD-878 (Box 7)
  - Scent of Heather, 1980; V-6528 (Box 7)
  - Scent uVA Butch, 1998; V-6529 (Box 8)
  - Scent uVA Butch, 1998; V-6530 (Box 8)
  - Score, 1972; V-6531 (Box 8)
  - Score, 1972; DVD-879 (Box 8)
  - Scum, 1991; V-6533 (Box 8)
  - Secret Files of J. Edgar Hoover, V-6534 (Box 8)
  - Secret Life of Nina Hartly, 1994; V-6535 (Box 8)
  - Self-loving with Betty Dodson, 1998; V-6536 (Box 11)
  - Sensual Exposure, 1993; V-6537 (Box 8)
  - Seventh Sense, 1999; V-6538 (Box 8)
  - Seven Into Snowy, 1990; V-6539 (Box 8)
  - Sex After 50, 1991; V-6540 (Box 8)
  - Sex Is..., 1993; V-6541 (Box 8)
  - Sex Junkies, 1991; V-6542 (Box 8)
  - Sex World, 1979; V-6543 (Box 8)
  - Sexual Secrets, V-6544 (Box 8)
  - Sexual Fitness, 1993; V-6545 (Box 8)
  - Sexual State of The Union, 1997; V-6546 (Box 11)
  - Sexual State of The Union, 1997; V-6547 (Box 11)
  - Shock, 1995; V-6548 (Box 8)
  - Shanes World Volume 12, 1998; V-6549 (Box 8)
  - Shanes World Volume 31, 2002; V-6550 (Box 8)
  - Showgirl Superstars, Chris Cassidy's Fantasies, 1982; V-6551 (Box 8)
  - Show Master, 1995; V-6552 (Box 11)
  - Sick Honey (or Slick Honey?), 1991; V-6553 (Box 8)
  - Sick, 1997; V-6554 (Box 8)
  - Sinners I, 1989; V-6555 (Box 8)
  - Slaves, 1988; V-6556 (Box 8)
  - Slippen in Through the Outdoor, 1995; V-6557 (Box 8)
  - Smoker, 1983; V-6558 (Box 8)
  - Snake Eyes I, 1989; V-6559 (Box 8)
  - Snoop Dogg's Doggystyle, 2001; DVD-880 (Box 8)
  - Snoop Dogg's Hustlaz, 2002; V-6561 (Box 8)
  - Snuff, V-6562 (Box 8)
  - Sodom and Gomorrah: The Last Days, 1986; V-6563 (Box 8)
  - Spacey Reel Productions, V-6604 (Box 11)
  - Star Angel, 1986; V-6564 (Box 8)
  - Still Insatiable, 1999; V-6565 (Box 8)
  - Stripped Bare, 2008; V-6566 (Box 11)
  - Stud Hunters, 2003; V-6567 (Box 8)
  - Suburban Dykes, 1990; V-6568 (Box 8)
  - Suburban Dykes, 1990; V-6569 (Box 9)
  - Suburban Dykes, 1990; V-6570 (Box 9)
  - Sugar High Glitter City, 2001; V-6571 (Box 9)
  - Sugar High Glitter City, 2001; V-6572 (Box 9)
  - Sulka's Wedding, 1983; V-6573 (Box 9)
  - Sulka's Wedding, 1983; V-6574 (Box 9)
  - Sunset Bull, 1994; V-6575 (Box 9)
  - Susie & Jon & Rudy, V-6576 (Box 9)
  - Susie Bright: Sex Pest, V-6577 (Box 11)
  - Susie Bright: Sex Pest, DVD-883 (Box 11)
  - Susie Bright Dailies parts 1+2, DVD-884 (Box 11)
  - Susie Bright Dailies part 3, DVD-885 (Box 11)
  - Susie Bright on Film and Video, DVD-886 (Box 11)
  - Susie on Fox News, 1980; V-6582 (Box 11)
  - Swamp, 1990; V-6583 (Box 9)
  - Swedish Erotica Volume 31, 1981; V-6584 (Box 9)
  - Sweet Dreams, 1979; V-6585 (Box 9)
    Annotation by Susie: Education availability only
  - Sweet Dreams, 1979; V-6586 (Box 9)
  - Sweet Revenge, 1986; V-6587 (Box 9)
  - Taboo V, 1986; V-6588 (Box 9)
  - Take Off, 1978; V-6589 (Box 9)
  - Talk TV Canada Susie Interview CBC, V-6590 (Box 11)
  - Talk to Me Baby, 2000; V-6591 (Box 9)
  - Tampa Tushy Fest Part 1, 1998; V-6592 (Box 9)
  - Tampon Tango, 1984; V-6593 (Box 9)
  - Tangerine, V-6594 (Box 9)
  - Taste of Ambrosia, 1987; V-6595 (Box 9)
  - Taste of Black, 1987; V-6596 (Box 9)
  - Tenderloin Tapes I Buddy Can You Spare a Dime, 1995; V-6597 (Box 9)
  - Tenth Annual Video Awards, V-6598 (Box 11)
  - That’s Outrageous, 1983; V-6599 (Box 9)
  - Therese & Isabelle, 1968; V-6600 (Box 9)
  - Therese & Isabelle, V-6601 (Box 9)
  - Therese & Isabelle, V-6602 (Box 9)
  - Three A.M., 1975; V-6603 (Box 9)
  - Three A.M., 1975; DVD-881 (Box 9)
  - Three A.M., 1975; V-6605 (Box 9)
  - Three A.M., 1975; V-6606 (Box 9)
  - Three Daughters, 1986; V-6607 (Box 9)
  - Tokyo Torture Chamber, 20001; V-6608 (Box 10)
  - Tonya and Jeff's Wedding Night, 1994; V-6609 (Box 10)
  - Too Big for His Britches, 1988; V-6610 (Box 10)
  - Touch Me, V-6611 (Box 10)
  - Traci I Love you, 1987; V-6612 (Box 10)
  - Trannie Boy Toys, 2003; V-6613 (Box 10)
  - True Legends of Cinema, 2003; V-6614 (Box 10)
  - True Love, 1989; V-6615 (Box 10)
  - Up!, 1976; V-6616 (Box 10)
  - Urban Friction, 2002; V-6617 (Box 10)
  - User Friendly, 1992; V-6618 (Box 10)
  - Victoria Falls, 1999; V-6619 (Box 10)
  - Videos for Lovers v. 1, 1993; V-6620 (Box 10)
  - Videos for Lovers v. 2, 1993; V-6621 (Box 10)
  - Videos for Lovers v. 2, 1993; V-6622 (Box 10)
  - Videos for Lovers v. 3, 1993; V-6623 (Box 10)
  - Videos for Lovers v. 4, 1993; V-6624 (Box 10)
  - Videos for Lovers v. 5, 1993; V-6625 (Box 10)
  - Videos for Lovers v. 6, 1993; V-6626 (Box 10)
  - Virgin Machine, 1988; V-6282 (Box 10)
  - Vixen, 1968; V-6286 (Box 10)
  - Vixen 2 (Supervixens), 1975; V-6298 (Box 10)
  - We Are Ourselves, 1976; V-6325 (Box 11)
  - Wet Rainbow, 1974; V-6331 (Box 10)
  - Where the Boys Aren't 5, 1995; V-6340 (Box 10)
  - Wild Bunch part I, 1969; V-6354 (Box 10)
  - Wild Bunch part II, 1969; V-6357 (Box 10)
  - Women's Motorcycle Festival 1987, 1987; V-6379 (Box 11)
  - Women's Sex Organs Revealed, 1998; V-6399 (Box 10)
  - Woods Resort Burlezk, Live, 1998; V-6403 (Box 10)
  - Worlds Biggest Gang Bang II, 1996; V-6426 (Box 10)
- Audio recordings
  Interviews with Susie and others.
  - Andrea Dworkin at San Fransisco State University, April 25, 1984; tr-9684 (Box 12)
  - Susie's Shaved Slice of Sin, 1994; tr-9685 (Box 12)
    Topics include Chris Kathman
  - Eithne Johnson Interviews Susie Bright, March 1994; tr-9686 (Box 12)
  - Eithne Johnson Interviews Susie Bright, March 1994; tr-9687 (Box 12)
  - Gon Buurman, June 1994; tr-9688 (Box 12)
  - Phyllis Christopher, October 18, 1994; tr-9689 (Box 12)
  - Phyllis Christopher, October 18, 1994; tr-9690 (Box 12)
  - Tee Corinne, November 12, 1994; tr-9691 (Box 12)
  - Tee Corinne, November 12, 1994; tr-9692 (Box 12)
  - Tee Corinne, November 12, 1994; tr-9693 (Box 12)
  - Tee Corinne, November 12, 1994; tr-9694 (Box 12)
  - Della Grace, November 1994; tr-9695 (Box 12)
  - Cathy Lee Prochazka, November 1994; tr-9696 (Box 12)
  - Cathy Lee Prochazka, November 1994; tr-9697 (Box 12)
  - Claire Garozilte, December 1994; tr-9698 (Box 12)
  - Kiss 'n Tell, December 4, 1994; tr-9699 (Box 12)
  - Kiss 'n Tell, December 4, 1994; tr-9700 (Box 12)
  - Katie Niles, December 1994; tr-9701 (Box 12)
  - Katie Niles, December 1994; tr-9702 (Box 12)
  - Jessica Tanzer, January 1995; tr-9703 (Box 12)
  - Shari Cohen, January 1995; tr-9704 (Box 12)
  - Shari Cohen, January 1995; tr-9705 (Box 12)
  - Romy Suskind, January 1995; tr-9706 (Box 12)
  - Romy Suskind, January 1995; tr-9707 (Box 12)
  - Jill Posener, January 1995; tr-9708 (Box 12)
  - Jill Posener, January 1995; tr-9709 (Box 12)
  - Dawn Lewis, January 1995; tr-9710 (Box 12)
  - Dawn Lewis, January 1995; tr-9711 (Box 12)
  - Honey Lee Cottrell, January 16, 1995; tr-9712 (Box 12)
  - Honey Lee Cottrell, January 16, 1995; tr-9713 (Box 12)
  - Barbie Painter, January 1995; tr-9714 (Box 12)
  - Wendy Chapkis, February 7, 1995; tr-9715 (Box 12)
  - Hunter Thompson, June 2000; tr-9716 (Box 12)
- Periodicals
  Publications containing articles by Susie Bright or about Susie Bright and various publications collected by Bright.
  - Susie Bright Related Periodicals
    - 1984 International Lesbian/ Gay Freedom Day Parade and Celebration program, June 24, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      Includes article by Susie Bright, "Year of the Lustful Lesbian".
      Volume/Issue:
      Publisher: Gay Freedom Day Committee
    - Feminary, Winter/Spring 1985 (Box 21)
      Includes an article by Susie Bright, Book Review of Lesbian Sex by JoAnn Loulan.
      Volume/Issue: Volume 14, Winter
      Publisher: Golden Gate Business Association
    - GirlJock, 1991 (Box 21)
      Cover story about Susie Bright. "Susie Bright On Girl Jocks" by Roxxie.Volume/Issue: Freezin' Season Issue 5
      Publisher: GirlJock TM publishing
    - High Times, November 1994 (Box 21)
      Includes article "Sex, Drugs and Susie Bright" by Marcy Sheine.r Volume/Issue: No. 231
      Publisher: Trans-High Corporation
    - Hip Mama, The Parenting Zine, 1998 (Box 21)
      Includes an article by Susie Bright, "Nuclear Family Meltdown."
      Volume/Issue: Number 16, 2nd Quarter
    - Hustler, March 1986 (Box 21)